<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Seed Backup Card</string>
    <string name="app_name_abbr">SBC</string>

    <!-- button label -->
    <string name="backup">Backup</string>
    <string name="restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="check_card">Check Card</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>

    <!-- input field label -->
    <string name="pin">PIN</string>
    <string name="backup_msg">Backup Message</string>

    <!-- input field error message -->
    <string name="cant_be_blank">This field can\'t be blank</string>

    <!-- input field placeholder backup message short version -->
    <string name="dummy_backup_msg">resource crush foil rocket stereo please sort work resource
        weird win rocket cat hidden scout milk era wage metal settle surge noodle run great</string>
    <!-- input field placeholder backup message long version -->
    <string name="dummy_backup_msg_long">These violent delights have violent ends and in their triumph die,
        like fire and powder, which, as they kiss, consume. The sweetest honey Is loathsome in his
        own deliciousness and in the taste confounds the appetite. Therefore love moderately;
        long love doth so; too swift arrives as tardy as too slow.</string>

    <string name="dummy_backup_msg_extremely_long">As most of my readers know, I’m an optimist.
        \nThis belief applies across my life, and to various investments as well. So I am intrigued by the
        success of cryptocurrencies, such as Bitcoin and Ethereum. The competition they are putting
        up against the gold standard looks insane, as Bitcoin goes off to the races.
        There’s no way to fully understand what’s going on in the crypto world — and I am not even
        sure anyone could if you tried to. Still, I can tell you that Bitcoin’s recent surge is
        really an opportunity to buy long-term real assets.
        \nCryptocurrencies are new and don’t even have a useful underlying technology.
        They will probably fail, probably sooner than later. If people forget about them quickly,
        it is likely to be because the underlying technology will finally mature and win out.
        We don’t even know whether that will happen in a generation or maybe a century,
        but it’s still possible it might.
        \nWhy invest in crypto now, if it’s unlikely to last?
        \nThe crypto world is more than one day old, and a lot of its early enthusiasts are
        looking back at what they did wrong. But most are still in it.
        There is still a lot of potential, and potentially a lot of wealth to be made.
        \nImagine the world right now, say 10 years from now. Have you invested in things like gold,
        real estate, or corporations?
        \nDo you think your assets will continue to appreciate,or will you have lost out to inflation
        and depreciation?\nGold has a history of doing that, but with corporate stock I’d be worried. Why?
        If you look at the past, corporate stocks and bonds aren’t exactly reliable long-term
        sources of capital. They tend to move in the same direction, and in the short run they tend
        to go down.
    </string>
    <!-- input field placeholder PIN -->
    <string name="dummy_pin">0000</string>
</resources>
